themafiaboss.com 2011-12-31

# The Mafia Boss Game Privacy Policy

Any private information received by TheMafiaBoss WILL NOT be given out to anyone or any organization; it WILL NEVER be sold or distributed in any form, or for any purpose unless approved by the account holder. Therefore, client information collected by TheMafiaBoss is the property of TheMafiaBoss and is not shared with any third party, including merchants. 

TheMafiaBoss is dedicated to providing useful, relevant and valuable information to our customers and subscribers. To do this, we offer an assortment of ongoing, daily, weekly and monthly publications. By opting to receive email from TheMafiaBoss.com a client is automatically subscribed to all its publications: 

Special Promotional Offers - Ongoing Receive information and/or offers on any new promotion or event. 

Service Announcements - As Needed Important messages concerning any temporary site or system outages, plus any maintenance issues that may affect the level of service. 

News Releases - Ongoing Receive all the latest breaking news and launch of new games and industry trends, including announcements of all new TheMafiaBoss options and features. 

To assure the quality of client communications, TheMafiaBoss provides clients with the opportunity to view or modify their subscription preferences at any time simply by logging into their account. 

It is possible for a client to opt-out of receiving email from TheMafiaBoss.com; however, there is a minimum level of communication needed for a client to play effectively, so everyone with a TheMafiaBoss account will receive a "Welcome" email, containing valuable account information, along with "Service Announcements". 

If at any time a client indicates that he or she no longer wants to receive communications from TheMafiaBoss, or if he or she wishes to change or correct any previously provided information, the client may send an email the customer service center. 

Qualified TheMafiaBoss staff have access to account holder names and email addresses. Clients can change their password directly on the TheMafiaBoss web site. 

If a client needs to change their email address, they should submit their changes directly from the TheMafiaBoss web site. 

Clients who lose their account login information may retrieve it via the "Lost password" option found in the "Log In" box of the TheMafiaBoss web site. All changes made to account holder information, whether done online or by email, are logged. It is the policy of TheMafiaBoss not to change an account holder's name unless we have an official name change notification on file (e.g. marriage certificate, notice of name change). 

If an individual becomes aware that personal information we maintain about that individual is inaccurate, or if an individual would like to update or review his or her personal information, the individual may contact us using the contact information below. As a security precaution, we may request that the individual provide identifying information such as name, birth date, etc. In addition, we may limit or deny access to personal information where providing such access would be unreasonably burdensome or expensive in the circumstances. 

TheMafiaBoss uses cookies to track how and when customers use the site. Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web surfing easier by saving your passwords and other preferences for you. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you'll find most major web sites use them. Cookies also help us to see which areas of the site are popular and which are not. We can then improve the site based on this information. 

TheMafiaBoss also log IP addresses for system administration purposes. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your playing account. 

TheMafiaBoss website contains links to other sites; we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

TheMafiaBoss will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. TheMafiaBoss will obtain your opt-in consent for any updates to this Privacy Policy that materially expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Policy at the time of collection. 

Contact Information 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, feel free to contact us at support@TheMafiaBoss.com 

Last Update: 07/09/2008
